Over 8 years of experience with the professional restaurant industry, excels at learning and taking on new responsibilities and their challenges all while applying them effectively. Promoted to positions of increasing responsibility by exceeding overall performance and expectations. Extremely versatile and can apply diverse knowledge and skill set to any position or field where given the opportunity to shine.

Selected Highlights

- Strong communication skills, both written, verbal, and artistically.
- Proficiency providing quick solutions when faced with complex situations.
- Expertise working with a diverse array of technologies and software.
- Strong multitasking skills, capable of managing several large tasks efficiently.
- Diverse experiences working independently or with others, having the flexibility to collaborate, manage or follow, all while being able to see through with responsibilities and tasks no matter the impact or scale.

Professional Experience

Ranazul – Fulton, MD

2009 - Present

Manager 2017 - Present

In my time at Ranazul I became extremely knowledgeable and comfortable with the daily operations of the business. While working a management position, I was capable of proving that I not only understood how to run the business but was able to prove it in practice. This transition has given me the confidence to take on any challenge that may come ahead.

Responsibilities:

- Managing inventory and scheduling third party services to ensure that the business was prepared for daily operations.
- Monitoring and interacting with the company's accounts, balancing cash and credit card transactions against sales, and depositing proceeds and ensuring proper change needs.
- Training and knowledge sharing with new hires, additionally ensuring their readiness for their position with the business, as well as scheduling management.
- Directly communicated with customers and ensured their satisfaction with the goal to maintain the reputation and image of the business.
- Ensuring the business and its employees were adhering to multiple policies and regulations.

Server / Expediter 2009 - 2017

Starting from the ground floor I had worked various positions with the business which provided me with a diverse set of experience and exposure to different responsibilities.

Education

Full Sail University – Music Production Bachelor of Science

2016 - Present

Volunteer Work & Extra Curricular Experience

Junior Reserve Operations Training Corps

Operations and Training Officer (2010-2012), Drill Team Commander (2010-2012)